Today in this video we will talk about the
best top three health insurance
policy plans of ICICI Lord. We will learn and
understand them. So if you are looking to get
a good and better health
insurance policy plan from ICICI Lord for yourself or your family, then
you can take any of the three policies that I am going to tell you about in this video.
I am telling
you about these three policies after comparing them with the health policy of ICICI Lord
because these three policies
provide better benefits than others, which is beneficial for you only. So
without much delay, let us directly
know about those three policies. At the
first place in this list is
Max Protect. For children, the
entry age on this policy is from 91 days to 21 years.
For adults, it is from 21 years to 65 years. There are
two types of plan options
available here, first is Classic and second is Premium. The
sum insured on both the plans ranges from ₹ crore to
unlimited, that is
Unlimited coverage is available, which is a
great thing. The tenure of this policy is from one to
three years. If you take it for two or three
years, you get a discount of 10% to 15% on your premium. There is
no capping on room rent; all rooms are covered. The
pre-hospitalization period is
60 days in both plan options,
and the post-hospitalization period is
180 days in both. AYUSH treatment is also
covered in both plans, for which there is no
limit. If you do
not make a claim in any year, you get a bonus of 20% that year,
which can be up to 100%.
Home care treatment is also available only
in the premium plan, up to ₹1 lakh.
Worldwide coverage up to ₹1 crore is also available only in the premium option
and is
not available in the classic plan. If we
talk about health checkups, this
coverage is also available only in the premium plan, at the rate of
₹1000000 per day.  And
not on the classic option, there is no co-payment here.
If you want to take this policy,
then take only the premium plan, only then
you will be more benefited. Similarly, many
other good benefits are
available here. Now the next second policy is
Complete Health Insurance. The sum insured on this policy ranges from
₹ lakh to ₹ crore.
Here the entry age is from 6 years and there is
no limit and for children it is from 3
months to 5 years. Its policy
period is one, two and three years. There is no room rent
capping in it, which
depends on the plan options and co-
payment is optional here. If you want to take it, you can
take it and if not, then no.
Total four types of plan options
are available on this policy, out of which the first is Health Shield, here the
sum insured ranges from ₹ lakh to ₹ lakh.
In this, the pre and post
hospitalization period is of 30 and 60 days.
Now the next updated version plan of this is
Health Shield Plus, in this sum insured is  The sum insured is
available from ₹ lakh to ₹ crore. Here the
pre and post hospitalization period is of
60 and 180 days. Now the next plan
option is Health Elite. Here also the sum
insured is available from ₹ lakh to ₹ 50 lakh
and here also the pre and post
hospitalization period is of 30 and 60 days
and the next updated version plan of this
is Health Lite Plus. Here the sum insured is
available from ₹ lakh to ₹ crore and the
pre and post hospitalization period is of 60
and 180 days. Similarly, many
other good
benefits are available on this policy too, so you
can choose the plan options as per your need.
Now the next third policy is Event.
Almost all the benefits are available in it. Its
entry age is from 18 years to 125 years. The
sum insured is from ₹ lakh to ₹ crore
and there is unlimited beyond that, that is, there is no limit.
No, it is of Sum Institute which is a very
good thing, the tenure of this policy is 1 year, 2
years and 3 years, here the pre and post
hospitalization period is 90 and 180 days,
room rent is covered up to single private AC room,
reset benefit is 100%, sum
insured is available unlimited times, there are
different types of cards available here
from which you can choose as per your need,
similarly, many other
good benefits are available here too, so
these are the top three best
health insurance policy plans of ICICI Lord, so if you
want to take it, you can take it, but
before taking any policy, read and understand its terms and
conditions properly,
take it only after that so that you do
not face any problem later at the time of claim, okay, so
let's go, if you liked the video then like it
and if you are new then definitely subscribe to the channel, we will meet
in the next video, till then Jai Jai bye bye